Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous!
We like it serious, serious, oh!
Looking deep in the dream,
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls built between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
Believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears.
In the world we're in.
United gently bringing up.
Our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones
we love, we'll carry on.
Till we see the light, the sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core
is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The bombs filled between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know, that's
what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, we're the superpowers.
I hope you enjoy the sensation of
candy slowly seeping into your bodies.
It's no use.
You can't break free. It's over.
Don't give up yet, Chopper.
Sweet release will come soon enough.
My goodness.
You must have been on
quite the sugar high if
you thought you could take
your ship back from us?
Admittingly, you put up
a good fight at first.
But I'm sorry to say you ran
over your heads from the starch.
We had soldiers stationed around the
island on lickety lookout for you.
You really had nowhere to run.
Our difference in strength is clear!
Pathetic.
Dammit! No!
I can't transform!
Let Tupper go! I beg you!
It's far too late for that.
This is what happens when
you decide to defy me.
I turn you into a candy
man and devour you.
The sugarcoating will cover your
entire body and permeate your insides.
It'll lickety-leave you in complete
agonies that robs you of your last breath.
The whole process only
takes about three minutes.
You're sick.
Oh, I just can't wait.
I'll be looking at two
sweet candied corpses.
No, hang in there!
That's enough!
A little too late to reconsider my offer.
I gave you several chances to escape,
but you two thought you knew better?
and chose this fate yourself.
You don't have a lick of
wisdom, so have sweet dreams.
And a bitter defeat.
Clupper, no!
Time's a-ticking, so
let the countdown begin.
You're only getting what
you deserve, I'm afraid.
Wait, reconsider this!
No one likes bones in their candy!
No!
I'll turn you into a candy man.
And lick you down to nothing.
Hey, Press.
That must be Mama.
Ready?
Her hunger pangs won't
lickety let up. Cake!
We had better start ignoring
Mama to pudding on Cacao Island.
If she finds out there's no wedding cake
on this ship, she will lickety kill me.
I don't think we're at that stage yet.
I want it!
We made it!
Hurry up and get on the Sunny!
Link, Straw Hats are still alive!
How is that possible?
But lightning must have
taken out our own forces.
Who's up there?
The Sunny has been hijacked!
Oh no! Rook! Chopper!
What happened to them?
Return to the mirror world.
You've only got a few seconds at most
before you're all lying at his feet.
It's Pierre Sparrow and Katakuri.
Of course it had to be those two.
I'm afraid we aren't
in the clear just yet.
Coo-coo-coo-coo.
Impressive that you've
been able to get this far.
I underestimated you.
But just to make it abundantly
clear, Your fun-ins now.
This is your final resting place!
Candy Maiden!
What is candy?
I think that's underselling it a bit.
Lickety-look at what it can do!
Fishman Karate!
Ah!
A quick fist, go!
Can't move! Go! Go!
Please work!
I'm not done yet.
Underestimating me will bring your end!
Huh? What the heck?
Candy Maiden!
Decoration!
It's too big to deal with.
Now for my next trick.
No one will leave you alive.
Let's circle around to the ship.
I'd rather plow straight through.
Run!
Oh, is that fire?
His Devil Fruit ability!
It's like Luffy's!
Give me my cake!
No!
Here she comes!
What's the plan, Luffy?
We're surrounded!
Luffy, get Katakuri off of the sunny!
We'll focus on our departure!
I'm on it!
Follow me! Right!
That jerk!
He must have come here through the mirror!
Where is my wedding cake?
I certainly don't envy being on the
receiving end of her hunger pegs.
Good lickety-luck.
Harm-a-ment harnet!
Kong Kong!
Kong!
What the hell?
Why isn't my Haki working?
Chopper!
Brook, are you okay?
Don't give up yet!
Where's my cake?
Hey, Carrot.
Be prepared for a sudden
turn of events. What?
Listen closely.
I firmly believe Luffy and
his crew are those whom our
tribe and the Kozuki clan
have awaited for centuries.
The ones who will lead all of
us to the dawn of a new world!
Well, I see this now!
Are you there, Mondor?
Can you hear me?
Yeah, loud and clear.
We will lead you to arrange a ship
blockade around the southwest coast.
Immediately.
You got it, Press.
Click.
It said that we are to surround the coast.
Coup de what?
Please explain.
We'll use Coup de Burst.
This ship can leap a
whole kilometer ahead.
If we don't use it, Big Mom
is just going to sink us.
If you think it'll be enough to
escape her grasp, then I won't argue.
Okay, let's bet our getaway on that.
Hey, guys, I think Mom's here.
Thought you could run?
Hey, Carrot, go help Luffy set sail.
Hurry up!
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
I know it must be here someplace.
Now, where could it be?
Hey, Brooke, Chopper,
stay strong, my friends.
It'd be a bitter escape if you
two didn't make it with us.
We've located the Straw
Hats at the Southwest Coast.
Minister Amand from the
Nuts Island Tartt speaking.
We're approaching the target.
Those battleships are closing
in on us from the sea.
And Big Mom looms over us on land.
I'm afraid we're trapped in the middle.
Mommy, we have to get going!
I'm trying to.
I still have to load up two more
big barrels of cola, though.
Then let me handle this.
Go help prepare the coop,
do whatever it is, okay?
Thanks. I'm on it.
Let me wave!
What's that candy?
Just our luck we can't use
coo to burst like this!
Something up?
We hit a snag.
The Sunny is trapped in
some kind of sticky candy.
Take a good lickety look
at my candy. Wave's power.
I'll admire its perfection with you.
It's the tomb guy!
What should we do?
You turn my friend in
the ship back right now!
Candy creep!
This is getting dire.
Kaku!
Will mama lickity kick
your butts to the curb?
Will the cannons capsize you before then?
Look at you vermin!
Pathetic!
All your hope is lost!
Beast sword!
Karajishi!
You do realize my bounty is 700 million.
And what are you worth?
Surely you knew that you were way
out of your lickety-league, kitty.
How pitiful.
You avoided death by
the skin of your tongue.
I can't die just yet.
The dawn of the new world is coming soon.
I can't rest until I've seen it!
Ma-ma-ma-ma.
Well, aren't you a char?
I'll make it fifty years, then.
Enjoy the rest of your life!
I must hand it to you.
It was clever to sacrifice your left eye.
Mama has killed other men
for much less, you know.
But why do you want to live so badly?
Clamming up, huh? Well, fine.
So how old are you?
I'm 27.
You've had 50 years of your
lickety lifespan drained by Mama.
So that now puts you at 77. Seven.
Interesting.
I wonder how many years you've got left.
Doesn't matter.
I'll choose where to die myself.
Hm.
Enough about that.
You were captain of the
Nox pirates, weren't you?
Doesn't Nox mean night?
Ooh, that sounds rather dark.
What's with the negativity, huh?
Every night comes to an end, as they say.
In that case
Nox could mean Before the dawn
You Karoo understand
The men who I admire Are
awaiting the dawn of the
new world All I want is to
lay its foundation For them
If I have enough time
for that I can die happy
You once said That before the dawn
And Nox were synonymous
with one another, yes?
It's such a shame that the
only Nox you'll come to
know is the eternal darkness
that awaits in your death.
Not quite.
Roger!
Lord Odin!
Let me go, too!
I'll do anything!
Just give me a chance!
Sorry, kiddo.
You're not quite ready yet.
I'm not a kid! I'm Pedro!
The truth is I don't have much time left.
Don't worry.
Everyone will have a day when
it's their moment to shine.
Wait and you'll see.
Trust me, you'll know
when your time has come.
You just got to stick it out until then.
It was nice meeting you, Pedro.
I get it. Thank you.
Pedro!
Huh?
It's Roger.
Whoa, what's with that look on your face?
Long ago, roger told me.
Everyone will get a chance to shine!
What are you rambling about?
It's finally my turn.
This should be more than enough
to undo all of your little tricks!
That's dynamite!
You wouldn't dare!
Have you lickety lost it?
I'm sorry, but I had a feeling
that this would be my final voyage.
What do you mean, Pedro?
Don't do it!
Adios.
What do you mean, Pedro?
One day, Yugara will
understand my decision.
No, it was to keep Luffy and his crew
alive so they can continue onward.
Pedro, no!
Listen, Yugaro must keep
moving forward! Pedro!
No, Press.
What?
Oh, I hope Mama and
Minister Perospero are okay.
It looks like they got blown up.
Their candy is melting down.
Is Press dead?
Did Pedro give up his life for us?
Was this truly the only
option that we had left?
I thought that was going to
be the end for me for sure.
Are you two all right?
No, Karen, it's too late. Let me go.
I need to help Pedro, don't he?
He might be alive out there. You can't.
You saw it too.
Pedro sacrificed himself for us.
He saved our lives because there
was no other way to escape.
Don't let his death be in vain.
Please, Karen.
Try the fly. Ready?
Yes, we're all set.
Hey, Chopper, Rock.
You guys still with us up there?
Huh?
Jinbei? Yes!
They're beginning to come around now!
Alright then, it's time to set sail!
Pedro bought us this time with his life!
No way I'm gonna let that go to waste!
We're getting out of here,
no matter what it takes!
I'm serious.
What's this about?
You're all so emotional!
Go away.
There's a second of death.
Careful, Carrot.
AHHHHHHH!
Straighten up, get on your feet, Carrot.
And take the blade once again.
She has no aptitude for swords.
Pedro!
It's none of your business!
Carrot will become a peerless
swordsman under my guidance!
There's more than one way to get stronger.
Surely there's another route
that's better suited for her.
What is this?
Take a fighting stance.
I have a feeling this may be
a better fit for you, Karoo!
It's better to play to your advantages.
I think you're quite
adept at aerial maneuvers,
so Combine that with your electro and
you, Karoo, will be off to a good start!
Seriously?
Uh-huh.
Try to attack me.
I'll be your sparring partner. Okie Dock!
I was starting to think I'd never
be strong like everyone else.
I can't believe the
answer was here all along.
Thanks for teaching me this!
It doesn't matter how you Karoo battle.
Just keep honing your skills
and be ready for anything.
I know you Karoo can do it.
Don't worry.
I know it?
You won't leave this
island as long as I'm here.
Get off of her! Right now!
Carrot, leave him to me!
You think you're strong
enough to kick me off?
We're leaving!
I'm the captain of this ship!
Now, Gum-Gum!
Elephant, don't go!
Sales look good towards the northwest.
Kaido burst azimuth 45
degrees to northwest!
Yes, going back will prevent
me from hurting your friends,
even if you can see what's coming?
You can't stop us from leaving!
Hey, brother, I'm here to save you!
No, not now.
I won't let them escape.
All units, prepare to
fire on the enemy ship.
Adjust elevation.
Mr.
Shark, it's time to boogie!
Help me, Chopper.
Grab ahold of the rope.
Let's pull our submersible
closer to the Sunny
before they start
attacking the poor thing.
Whoa, Carrot!
Think you can stand up?
Here, let me help you.
I'm all right.
Thank you, Tia Nami.
Where is it?
She caught up!
This is gonna be messy.
We have to get out of here quick
before she damages this Sunny anymore!
It can't be!
Is that Pedro?
So he did survive!
He almost had me.
That isn't Pedro!
It's Candy Guy!
He was actually fighting
for a second there.
That crazy mink lickety
left with my candy armor.
That's unfair!
Why is he alive?
And not Pedro!
It appears all our cannonballs
were intercepted this time!
Third round.
Hurry up and prepare the cannons.
Let go!
Carrot! Inami!
Jinbei!
Brook!
Chopper!
Listen up!
I'll be right back!
Can you hold down the fort?
Murphy, what are you two talking about?
When the lever returns to its original
position, the refill process is complete.
Okay, everybody.
Better hold on to something.
Death grip commenced.
Too ready for takeoff
when you are, Jinbei.
We're good over here, too!
Right! Let's go!
Don't let the target get away. Now fire!
It's time!
Lastly, don't forget to shout!
We're running!
Kaku now burst!
Burst!
Super!
Amand reporting in.
The enemy has escaped by air. It's what?
Hey, where's Loopy?
Is that Straw Hat?
What, get out of here!
Well played.
Now I can fight you
without any interruptions.
No way!
That was his path back!
What the hell is that guy thinking?
So that's your captain's
determination, Val.
But you're no match for me.
This place will be your grave.
No, I'll go back to the sunny,
right after I kick your ass!